I'm digging myself out of this
dig myself out
of this graveyard. [music]
[music]
Nothing but misery and loneliness
under the ground. Surrounded by
skeletons that were lost and never
[music] found.
Buried in good places. But it's time for
me to get out. And it's [music] time to
leave the dead [singing] things. I'm
feeling I want to be now.
[music]
I'm taking myself down.
Ready [music]
to stand
[music]
out.
>> Hey, Waxwell isn't singing at all. He's
just mouththing to the words.
>> Typical wacky Waxwell with his wacky
scams. I can't believe he got shrimp fin
and gooin on this.
>> I want my money back.
How much money did we make? $2.
Ginger, look. This is what I'm going to
be doing to Cosmo later.
He's joking, obviously.
Lower. Higher. I said higher. Just tell
me where you want it. You're the
supercomputer. Can't you tell where it
would look the best yourself? Well,
clearly your idea of best is not the
same as mine.
See, this combative personality you've
got, V, is the reason Shelly won't kiss
you.
Did every tune in the book club finish
reading Spooky the Square Pumpkin over
the weekend? There's so much I want to
talk about. I felt so seen by how ugly
and different Spooky was compared to all
the other pumpkins in the pumpkin patch
because I'm often told I'm ugly, too.
>> Yes, Squirm.
>> Can I please recommend the book we read
next weekend?
>> Oh, Squirm, Razle's book recommendation
is next week. Then Dazzle's book is the
week after that. Then it's Britney's
turn. I'm sorry.
>> You'll get your turn eventually. You're
the book club's newest member, so you
need to see how things are run around
here first.
>> Yeah. We're not discriminating against
you just cuz you're fat.
Ah.
>> Oh, hi Dandy. Do you want to sit in on
our book club?
>> Thanks Astro, but reading is for homos.
>> Oh, I can't wait to go trick-or-treating
tonight.
>> Yeah, about that squirm. There's another
reason I stopped by. I decided to pass a
one-day ordinance for the town of Garden
View. It says here that for Halloween,
Squirm must stay indoors to protect the
town's candy supply since he is so fat.
>> Ah,
knock on the door, Gordy. And remember
to say trick or treat.
Trick or treat.
TRICK OR TREAT. AH, CRACKERS. We're
wearing the same thing. What do you
think you're doing wearing that? What
are you saying? Sprout can wear it cuz
he has a smoking hot athletic strawberry
build, but I'm not allowed to cuz I'm a
chubby chubster.
Obviously, go put on a shirt or a bra or
something. There are child tunes out
here. You did this on purpose to spite
me, Dandy. Now, please explain how I
knew we were both going to be the same
thing for Halloween. Because when I lent
you Robux and my phone to buy a
Halloween costume off the Roblox store,
you would have seen the costume I had
picked out sitting in the cart. Well, I
clicked purchase first. You should have
went and picked a different costume if
you were so worried about us matching.
You're just mad that I look better in it
than you do.
>> Mr. Seedley, I want candy.
>> Gordy, what a cute little costume you've
got.
>> It's not cute. It sucks.
>> Hi, Shrimpo and Finn. Did you make those
costumes yourselves?
>> We sure did, kiddo. We're jellyfish.
Watch this.
Ah, come on, Shrimpo. It looks way
cooler when we sway together.
Watch where you're swaying.
>> You're the one who bumped into me.
>> Vinn Shrimpo, stop fighting. You two are
dating, right? Boyfriends aren't
supposed to fight.
>> Boyfriends? Gosh, is that how we look to
others?
>> We absolutely are not boyfriends.
>> Gordy, you startled us. What do you
want?
Why are you walking with us? You're
being a creep. I'm not doing it on
purpose. I need to go this way to meet
up with Astro and Dial in the park.
Astro and Dial. Is it weird to you that
I have friends? No, it's just Dial is
your ex. And isn't Astro your new boy
toy? Is it a good idea to get them
together? What if they start acting
territorial over you like crazed beasts?
Astro isn't my boy toy. You know I'm not
gay anymore. And Astro isn't either.
Plus, Dial and I can still be friends
despite being exes. Dial asked me to go
trick-or-treating with him this year.
And I've been ignoring him for so long.
I just think it's time to try rekindling
our friendship. And Astro doesn't have
any other friends and would have no one
to trickor treat with if I just ditched
him. Trick or treat.
>> Trick or [music] treat. Trick or treat.
Trick or treat.
Last I checked, sweetheart, wizards
aren't exactly known for carrying around
AAC units. [laughter]
>> I didn't get any candy again.
>> That homo gave me two pieces. Do you
want one of mine?
>> No, I want to get my own candy.
>> Scraps. How are you doing?
>> The best ever. I've gotten so much
candy.
>> And your little brother, Goob?
>> Who cares how he's doing? He's autistic.
>> Roger. I love your costume.
>> Oh, thank you. Toodles tells me it looks
better with the hood up. I typically
don't partake in holiday festivities
since at my age the young ones tend to
call me cringe, but Toodles wanted to do
matching costumes.
>> Well, I think you look cute and
breathable for an old man who says
there's an age limit for tunes to dress
like a thirsty twink.
>> Here, Scraps. Take this candy. I've just
been giving away all the candy I'm
collecting because otherwise it would
all go to my fat butt.
>> Oh boy. Do I get some, too?
What is this?
>> It's one of those books with different
cloths to feel. Since you're mentally
challenged, I figured you would prefer
that over candy.
>> I want candy.
>> Goob, I'm sorry. I I thought it would
make you happy.
Dandy over here.
>> You're 5 minutes late, though. I suppose
that's better than being half an hour
late like you were to all of our meetups
back when we were dating.
>> Dial our one agreement tonight is that
we would leave everything in the past.
>> Razle and Dazzle have a food cart set up
over there. Want to go get a pretzel?
Oh, I don't have enough money. Daddy's
got you, baby girl.
Um, I want to get the cream cheese
filled ones. Those cost a dollar more.
Also, I want a can of Pepsi to wash it
down with. I don't need a Pepsi.
Oh, it's so good. Dandy, do you want
some?
>> No.
>> Shall we be making our way through the
neighborhood then? I hear the circus
trio is giving out full-sized candy
bars, so if I may suggest, that should
be our first stop of the night. Danny
and I usually skip Yata Louie and Blat's
house.
>> Why is that? They always go with a
haunted carnival theme in their front
yard. And you know, I don't do well with
scary stuff.
>> Just stay close by me and if you get
scared, you're free to grab onto my arm.
>> Dead ass. Or one of mine. I've got four
of them.
>> Gross deformed freak of nature.
>> Dial. You can think it, but you can't
say it.
>> You're right. I'm sorry, Astro.
>> It's okay. I'm used to it.
I told you their house has a lot of
creepy decorations. I don't know if I
can do this.
>> Did I get you good dandy?
>> Don't do that, Louie.
Hey, look, Cosmo. Isn't that your cousin
Ginger's house? Why don't we stop there
next? Oh, yeah. Let's do that. Pick up
the pace, Gordy. You're falling behind.
>> I'm coming.
Oh, Sprout and Cosmo.
>> Trick or treat.
>> Aren't you going to give us candy?
>> Well, I don't know. A lot of tunes are
going to be sticking their hands in this
bowl and I don't want them catching
your, you know, your gay disease.
>> You mean AIDS? That's not how AIDS
works. Being gay isn't a disease,
Ginger. It doesn't work like that. I
just have to take precaution. You know
how it is.
Oh, hi Tisha. I love your bumblebee
costume. Here, I'll give you three
pieces of candy.
>> Sprout, can we go?
>> So, Cosmo, what's so important that you
wanted to talk about?
>> It's uh about how I've been feeling. I
can tell her if you want, Cosmo. Thanks,
Steamy Buns. But I want to be able to
say it myself. How do I put this,
Ginger? You know how I told you I've
been feeling off about something lately?
>> Yeah, but I thought it just had [music]
to do with you having runny poops.
>> That's what I said because it's hard to
talk about. What I'm dealing with is
more internal and has to do with Sprout.
>> Sprout also has runny poops.
>> No, but it does have to do with butt
stuff.
>> Ginger Eye, I think I like boys like
romantically. I know I'm not supposed
to, but I keep thinking about what it
would be like to hold a boy's hand or to
kiss them and and you know that kind of
stuff.
What do you mean you're gay? You've got
to be joking, right? Tell me this is
just a sick joke.
>> Ginger, I'm I'm sorry, Cosmo. You don't
have to apologize for this.
>> Don't we have enough homos with Glisten
in town? One is enough. What will all
the other tunes think about me? me
having a gay cousin. I'm going to be
bullied at the girl sleepovers because
of you. Why are you doing this to
[music] me? Do you hate me?
>> It's because I don't hate you that I
feel comfortable telling you this.
You're the only one who knows. I thought
you would be more understanding.
>> All I understand now is that you like
taking it up the butt. Worst birthday
ever. What? Did Sprout turn you gay? Did
he force himself on you? Quit crying and
talk to me. I've always had a feeling,
but lately I've been opening myself up
to Sprout, and he's been helping me
through it and [music] telling me it's
okay for me to be attracted to Boy
Tunes.
>> Well, it's not. He's wrong. I hate you.
I can't believe you hit me at my
birthday dinner.
>> Sprout, [music] stop it. Apologize.
Apologize to my kitten right now. Or do
you want me to punch off the other half
of your face, too?
Sprout, [music] I want to go home. Not
until Ginger says sorry. You've already
proven yourself to be the alpha male.
It's not this big a deal. It shouldn't
matter who Cosmo loves. You're supposed
to care about him because he's your
cousin. Why are you doing this? Why live
in a world of negativity when both yours
and our lives are made more difficult
because of it. It's tunes like you that
make it hard for tunes like us to live
and keep going, you monster.
>> So, do you want to go to the next house?
Hey, come on. You're fine. I don't feel
like I am.
Can we talk?
Hey, [music] you.
I think you're my sub.
[music]
I hear you.
Or am I wrong?
And now [music] I lose my love. My love
reaches out of my [music] mind. And you
and you are none more than a
[music]
So wave. Yeah. Wave. Can you even hold
me?
>> [music]
>> Hey, have you been keeping an eye on
Gordy?
When Dandy agreed on hanging out this
Halloween, he didn't tell me you were
going to be here.
>> Me and Danny always trickor treat
together. It's like our tradition.
>> Do you hate me, Astro?
>> Of course not.
>> You don't. You're Dandy's friend, which
makes you my friend, too. Right now, I'm
just happy being close to Dandy. Isn't
that enough for you, too?
>> Does Dandy ever talk about me?
>> All the time.
>> Really?
>> Of course.
>> But he hasn't talked to me directly in
over a year.
>> He's talking to you now. The love you
two had for each other was real. And
when you two broke up, it broke him.
>> Are you crying about Dial again?
>> We picked out our stupid costumes
together. I didn't expect to see him
wearing it.
>> You broke up with him only a week ago.
It's okay to cry.
It's because Dandy loved you that it
took him so long to get to this point
where he can even just have you around
as a friend.
[snorts]
I can't believe you lost Gordy. You had
one job. I'm trying to pee. All I'm
saying is just that it's not my fault. I
can't pee unless I'm concentrating. You
know this about me. Whatever.
It wasn't my job to keep an eye on
Gordy. I thought you didn't want to talk
about it. I just wanted to go
trick-or-treating with you like we do
every year because it's a fun little
date night for the two of us. I wasn't
prepared to also be playing babysitter.
>> I'm afraid we must put our Halloweeny
escapades on Whole Gang. Dandy needs our
help.
>> You lost Gordy. Gordy was right behind
us one second. And then when we turned
around, we noticed he wasn't there
anymore. So, we're thinking he either
got tired and went home or he was
kidnapped. Either way, it's whatever.
The only one who has to deal with it now
is whatever Toon Fiddler took him away.
Take us to the last place you saw him
right now. How long are we going to be
talking about this? I want to go back to
trick-or-treating. Sprout,
see nothing.
>> There seems to be a suspicious trail of
candy leaning from the sidewalk and into
the woods. It may be that Gordy himself
has left a trail behind for us to find.
>> See, Sprout, I told you the candy trail
was suspicious.
>> Be quiet, you mentally challenge loser.
>> I'm sorry.
>> We do need to be as quiet as possible.
If the tune who kidnapped Gordy dragged
him out to the forest, they can only be
up to something nefarious.
>> There's something nefarious going on.
All right.
It's not just Gordy, but the other
Halloween tunes, too. Sylvester,
Eclipse, and Rebecca. And look, it's my
book club friends, too. Razle and Dazzle
and Brighten. What in the Cinnamon Toast
Crunch is going on?
>> Who is that in the [music] Black Cloak?
>> Boxton. Oh, I'm sorry. I thought I was
alone out here.
>> Who is it? Show yourself,
>> Squirm. How could it be?
>> I'll tell you how it be, Dandy. This is
all your fault for your stupid town
ordinance that prevents me from
participating in today's activities. Why
does every other tomb get to have fun
and eat bucketloads of candy while I
don't? So, as revenge, I'm going to burn
the Halloween tunes and really make
Halloween a night to remember for all
the wrong reasons.
>> I mean, even if you want to live them,
we're still going to celebrate Halloween
next year cuz at the end of the day,
it's the only time we can get some free
candy. But go off, queen. Live your
truth. and Brightne and Razzle and
Dazzle Squirm. They are our friends.
>> If you guys were really my friends,
you'd have at least tried reading one of
my book recommendations. [screaming]
>> Now, this is where the real fun begins.
Starting with you, pretty boy.
>> Please, Squirm. You can't do this.
You're too physically attractive to be a
villain.
>> Shut up. I'm my own tune. I can do
whatever I want.
>> Style, you saved me.
>> Oh, I I did. [laughter]
>> Stop. Stop it.
>> Yeah, that's enough.
>> What are you tunes doing? Even after I
tried to burn you all alive? That may be
true, but you're still a part of our
book club, and that means a friend.
>> We're so sorry, Squirm. We were so awful
to you. Of course, you would want to
unal alive us.
>> We never read any of the books I want to
read. And even though it's my job to
bring the snacks, you never let me eat
any because I'm already fat. I feel like
this whole town hates me.
>> Oh, baby boy. Well, then at our next get
together, how about we read one of your
recommendations?
Oh. Um, I actually don't even got one. I
was just saying stuff. To be honest, I
can't even read. That's why I have so
little to comment on when we do go over
books.
>> You can have this one then. It's the
kind that has hardly any words in it, so
it's easy to read and has fun things
that you can feel.
>> And take some of my candy, too. If Dandy
and your book club pals won't let you
have some,
>> take some of mine, too. And mine.
>> And you can have some of ours. I'm not
giving that worm any of mine.
>> I'm glad you came tonight.
>> I wasn't sure you really wanted me here
when you first asked me out.
>> I wasn't sure either, but I really am.
>> It's been a long time since we spent
Halloween together. Yeah, I missed this.
Even if we didn't get to do many of the
festivities I was looking forward to.
>> Like what?
>> I don't know. Bobbing for apples,
pumpkin carving.
>> Then we will. It doesn't have to be
Halloween. We can do that stuff tomorrow
or the next day.
Even if it's after Halloween.
>> Really?
>> Yeah. I mean, we're friends again,
aren't we?
>> Yeah. friends.
>> When we broke up, I honestly thought
that was it. I figured we'd never sit
together and talk like this again. I
thought everything in the past would
just continue being, you know,
embarrassing stories I'd keep talking
about with Astro. He can believe we both
went through that little gay phase.
>> Dandy, it wasn't a phase for me. It
never was. You know that. I loved you. I
didn't stop just because we broke up.
Dial.
>> But [music] it's true.
>> You'll get over it. You'll meet someone
else.
>> Dandicus.
>> You'll realize you were confused. You'll
wake up one day and wonder what you ever
saw in me and in other boys in general.
>> You really think I don't know myself.
>> Maybe I do. Any tune can change who
they're attracted to.
>> You're just scared. You keep talking
like this is something you'll outgrow if
you choose to ignore it. But it's been a
year and everyone can see that you still
like boys the same way you used to like
me.
>> You don't know what you're talking
about.
>> I do. And it infuriates me. I must
admit.
>> I just wanted things to be normal
between us again.
>> I'll give you whatever you want.
>> No.
>> Just one night together will make it all
easy for the both of us again.
>> Easy nights made for exhausting days
back then. We were still happy if
exhausted.
>> You're not listening to me. You never
do. It's always what you want. I can't
open myself up to you as anything more
than as a friend. Because if we end up
fighting and stop talking again, I
couldn't take another year of that. What
will our rekindling have all been for?
>> Perhaps risking it all for what you want
is better than living a life pretending
you're someone you aren't.
>> Stop. Dial. Stop.
He said stop.
Crazy. [music]
I think about you lately.
I wish you
moved on and on and on.
[music]
>> [music]
>> [__] that baby. Now it's over.
We're heading out the door. The door.
The door. The door.
Yeah. [music]
[music]
>> [music]
>> Dreaming
[music]
heat.
No, there's no [music and singing] one
that makes me feel like you do, babe.
[__] these no [singing] ones.
No reason [music] not to go away.
I'm thinking old [singing] cars get last
[music]
n [music]
Heat. Heat.
[music]
Oh, there's [music] no [singing]
way I tried to be the rich babe. [music]
Let our [singing] problems
be worse.
[music]
I'm thinking old [singing] cars get a
lot smoke. [music]
[music]
[singing]
Heat. Heat.